menu

### Search

Privacy policy
==============

### Privacy Policy

#### Our commitment to our donors:

We will not sell, share, or trade our donors' names or personal information with any other entity, nor send mailings to our donors on behalf of other organizations. This policy applies to all information received by United Way of Rhode Island, both online and offline, on any platform ("platform" includes the United Way of Rhode Island website), as well as any electronic, written, or oral communications.

Privacy policy last updated: December 29, 2020

#### Our privacy policy

United Way of Rhode Island recognizes the importance of protecting the information we may collect from visitors to our websites and electronic platforms, including all sites and pages connected to unitedwayri.org, www.myfund.org and uwriweb.org. Our policy is to use the information we acquire from visitors to our sites for internal purposes only, and we maintain appropriate security measures to keep this information private. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using.

Users can visit our sites without revealing any information about themselves. If a visitor chooses to give us personal information via the internet for the purposes of correspondence, processing a gift, or providing a subscription to a publication, then it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information.

If users tell us that they do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact, we will respect their wishes. If users wish to review or correct the personal information we’ve collected, they can do so by contacting us at info@unitedwayri.org. We also keep track of the domains from which people visit, analyzing this data for trends, insights, and statistics. Afterward, we discard it.

Our websites are not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to our websites. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on these websites, register with these websites, use any of the interactive or public comment features of these websites, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we may have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [info@unitedwayri.org](mailto:info@uwri.org).

United Way of Rhode Island takes precautions to keep the user information disclosed to us secure, and such information will not be disclosed to third parties for commercial purposes. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. United Way of Rhode Island uses SSL encryption for all financial transactions to protect personal information.

#### Use of cookies

Certain sections of our website use “cookies” to store user information. A cookie is a small string of text that a website can send to your browser. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture your email address. Currently, websites use cookies to enhance the user’s visit; in general, cookies can securely store a user’s ID and password, personalize home pages, identify which parts of a site have been visited or keep track of selections in a “shopping cart.” Cookies help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our sites so we can make the user experience even better.

Cookies were originally designed to help a website distinguish a user’s browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. If you are just browsing United Way of Rhode Island’s website, a cookie identifies only your browser. If you become a registered user on a United Way of Rhode Island website (with a user ID and password), we may use cookies so that we can provide personalized information that we believe will be of value to you based on preferences you have indicated while visiting the site. It is possible to set your browser to inform you when a cookie is being placed—this way, you have the opportunity to decide whether to accept the cookie. If you are just browsing our site and are not a registered user, you do not have to accept a cookie and you can still continue browsing the site. However, if you are visiting a site where you will be accessing a confidential account, you must accept that site’s cookies because they are essential for site administration and security.

#### Questions and agreement

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, contact United Way of Rhode Island. If you do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, you may not use the site. It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for periodically visiting this privacy policy to check for any changes.

In the News

Press Releases

In the News

#### Five Questions With: Roshni Darnal

June 6, 2023

###### Providence Business News

Roshni Darnal is the director of community investments for [United Way of Rhode Island](https://www.unitedwayri.org/)... where she manages the organization's strategic direction to address the needs of Rhode Islanders through its grantmaking processes… Darnal spoke with [Providence Business News](https://pbn.com/) about those grantmaking changes and what it means for the nonprofit community moving forward.

#### FCARI: Prescription Delivery Services for Seniors

May 10, 2023

According to the Kaiser Family Foundation, 89% of adults 65 and older take prescription medicine. For seniors who have mobility issues or are unable to leave their homes to go to the pharmacy, using a prescription delivery service is a simple solution.

This resource provides seniors and their caregivers with the top prescription delivery services, information on financial assistance options, and guidance on choosing the best service for their specific needs. Learn more at: [www.caring.com/best-prescription-delivery-services/](https://www.caring.com/best-prescription-delivery-services/)

#### PBN announces 2023 Best Places to Work honorees

April 28, 2023

###### Providence Business News

Sixty-seven honorees, including [United Way of Rhode Island](https://www.unitedwayri.org/), have been named by Providence Business News for its 2023 Best Places to Work Awards program... The honorees will be recognized June 7 for their efforts in a [ceremony at Crowne Plaza Providence-Warwick in Warwick](https://pbn.com/event/2023-best-places-to-work/), where the company rankings in each category will be announced.

Press Releases

22 May

#### [United Way Hosting Equity Challenge](https://www.unitedwayri.org/press-release/united-way-hosting-equity-challenge/ "United Way Hosting Equity Challenge")

As part of United Way of Rhode Island’s ongoing commitment to and demonstration of diversity, equity, and inclusion, the organization is preparing to host its 2024 Equity Challenge. All Rhode Islanders, individuals, and families, as well as local businesses, organizations, and groups are invited to participate in the challenge, which is being offered at no \[…\]

15 Apr

#### [United Way Accepting Applications for Providence Equity Fund](https://www.unitedwayri.org/press-release/united-way-accepting-applications-for-providence-equity-fund-grant-program/ "United Way Accepting Applications for Providence Equity Fund")

In collaboration with the City of Providence and aligned with its mission to build racial equity and opportunities for all Rhode Islanders, United Way has issued a request for proposal (RFP) for the Providence Equity Fund grant program. Available funding is to support strategies that promote racial and social equity, economic mobility, and educational opportunities for underserved populations in Providence.

01 Mar

#### [United Way Hosts 12th Children’s Book Drive](https://www.unitedwayri.org/press-release/childrens-book-drive-2024-copy/ "United Way Hosts 12th Children’s Book Drive")

United Way of Rhode Island’s Children’s Book Drive is back! In April and May, we’re teaming up with Books Are Wings to help Rhode Island children build their own libraries at home. Join us by buying and shipping books, dropping off books at one of our collection sites, or hosting a drive.

UPCOMING EVENTS
---------------

08 Jun

#### [Day of Action](https://www.unitedwayri.org/event/day-of-action-2/ "Day of Action")

Saturday, June 8, 2024  
9 a.m. - 3:30 p.m.

Join us at United Way of Rhode Island to sort and label donated children's books!  
50 Valley Street, Providence, RI  02909

Morning shift  | 9 a.m. - 12 p.m.  
Afternoon shift | 12:30 - 3:30 p.m.

United Way LIVE UNITED t-shirts and refreshments will be provided.

12 Jun

#### [Women United Summer Social](https://www.unitedwayri.org/event/women-united-summer-social/ "Women United Summer Social")

Join Women United members for a summer social.

Wednesday, June 12, 2024  
5:30 - 8 p.m.

Cafe Nuovo, One Citizens Plaza, Providence

19 Jun

#### [Equity Challenge 2024](https://www.unitedwayri.org/event/equity-challenge-2024/ "Equity Challenge 2024")

June 19 - 27, 2024

Over the course of 7 days, employees throughout the state of Rhode Island will have the opportunity to participate in various activities, each designed to broaden perspectives and inspire meaningful conversations while demonstrating an individual and/or organizational commitment to equity.

10 Oct

#### [Annual Celebration 2024](https://www.unitedwayri.org/event/annual-celebration-2024/ "Annual Celebration 2024")

Save the date!

Thursday, October 10  
6 - 8 p.m.

Waterfire Arts Center  
475 Valley St., Providence

### Subscribe to add impact to your inbox

* First Name\*
    
* Last Name\*
    
* Email
    
* CAPTCHA

### Stay Connected

### Make a Gift. Help A Rhode Islander

Invest in high-quality childcare, summer and afterschool programs, job training, healthcare, food, housing, and utility assistance.

### Help Starts with 211

Three simple numbers. One human connection. 200,000 calls a year in Rhode Island. If you, or someone you know, needs help, dial 211.

### Support UWRI

Help a Rhode Islander today

© 2024 United Way of Rhode Island

Mon. - Fri.  
8:00 a.m. - 4:30 p.m.
